Guide to the Henry Ernest Sigerist Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Additional Material, 1891-1991; Accession 1997-M-042
  - Plans of work
    - 1932/1933-1933/1934 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - 1934/1935-1935/1936 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - 1936/1937-1937/1938 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - 1938/1939-1940/1941 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - 1941/1942-1942/1943 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - 1943/1944-1944/1945 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - 1945/1946-1946/1947 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - 1948 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - 1949-1951 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - 1952-1953, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Program [celebration on the 100th anniversary of Sigerist's birth at the Karl-Sudhoff Institut], 1991 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Visual materials
    - Albums
      - Swiss army, 1912-1917 (Box 2, Folder 21)
      - Leipzig Institute events
        - 1927-1929 (Box 3, Folder 22)
        - 1929-1930 (Box 3, Folder 23)
      - Greece, 1930 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Loose photographs
      - Sigerist, Henry
        - Portraits, 1909-1955 (Box 4, Folder 25)
        - With family or friends or at events, 1906-1916, 1946 (Box 4, Folder 26)
      - Acquaintances, undated (Box 4, Folder 27)
      - Family, undated (Box 4, Folder 28)
      - Places, 1932, undated (Box 4, Folder 29)
      - Trips to Soviet Union
        - Azerbaijan, undated (Box 4, Folder 30)
        - Crimea, undated (Box 4, Folder 31)
        - Tiflis, Georgia, undated (Box 4, Folder 32)
        - Unidentified, undated (Box 4, Folder 33)
- Additional material, 1957-1970; Accession 2005-M-069
  - Henry E. Sigerist Research Fund/Award
    - Correspondence, 1957-1970 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Minutes of committee meeting, 1963 December 7 (Box 1, Folder 2)